Shoot him down before he gets away!
Oops, I guess he spotted me.
He went inside the main gate!
Rufy passed by one gate only to find another.
This is the main gate!
I have an urgent message for the chief officer at the main island front gate!
It's an emergency!
This is Spondum, what's going on?
An intruder somehow managed to pass through the main gate
and is heading towards the main island, sir!
One intruder, that's what all this fuss is about?
Surely you can manage to take care of him.
But, sir, you don't understand!
This is the main island front gate.
Don't worry, we'll take care of things from here.
However, the marines weren't prepared for what they had coming.
Hey there, buddy, that's far enough.
Do you have the slightest idea where you are?
Don't take this guy lightly!
Unless my eyes deceive me, then I'm pretty sure that he'll...
The pirate straw hat, Lufy!
Whoo!
What?
What was that you just said?
The man with the 100 million weary bounty!
It is him!
Frohat Lufy!
Where's Robin?
Huh?
Tell me where Robin is right now!
This is the main gate with another urgent report, sir!
What is it this time?
There's a group of heavily armed men riding giant monsters over the gate!
We need reinforcements!
Please!
Don't waste a second!
Let's go!
Hello!
What's wrong?
Answer me!
What's going on here?
Soyan, movement
Be quiet
Floating ship
Boалась
hurstrap
Let's go
To CAD
ed
Hecommerce
We need reinforcements!
Please!
AAA star
We need reinforcements!
Don't waste a second!
Let's go!
Hello!
What's wrong?
Answer me!
What's going on here?
heid 差し
さてないこの
海をこえて
探しに行こうよ
誰も未だ
みつけられない
世界のキセキを
高鳴る胸
思いのまま
突き進むだけさ
ゆで
オリンピートが残す
足跡
I'll see you next time.
All right, guys.
You ready to roll?
Aren't you hurt?
Don't worry.
These wounds better not.
To Sniper King!
Only four minutes left.
Then the C-Train Rocket Man is gonna tear through.
Sorry to bother you, but could you let me pass?
Even if you ask nicely, you're still an intruder.
And no means no!
Fair enough.
But I'll warn you.
Get ready for a fight.
Bring it on, pirate!
Boosh!
Hey, that's Cheeky!
How can we attack him?
Boosh!
It's just a lame, childish trick.
Don't back down!
Ally Robot, punch!
No!
Ally Robot, kick!
I didn't mean to. I'm sorry.
I've had enough of your games.
Your back is wide open.
You!
Faster!
Bring him down!
There's only one of them!
Damn it! How does he do that?
I'm in a hurry.
But you'll have more people to fight later.
See ya!
Hey! Come back!
He went inside! After him, quick!
He made it to the main island!
Somebody contact the chief!
Right! I'm on it!
This is the front gate reporting.
I'm afraid Straw Hat Luffy has entered the main island, sir!
What? Why the hell did you let him do that?
What's going on over there?
What about Oimo and Cassie?
You can't tell me they got taken out too!
Well, it's actually the middle of the night right now, sir.
I'm thinking they're probably asleep.
Then stop yapping at me and wake them up!
And if any of the other gods are sleeping, wake them up too!
Uh, yes, yes, sir!
I don't get why everyone's pissing their pants over this.
What's one little intruder?
Just let us take care of him.
Nonsense!
This place is the entrance to the world government.
The judicial island isn't just a navy base.
It's a symbol of justice.
Any idiot should know what it means to attack any's lobby,
and if they don't, we'll have to teach them.
If we let some dirty band of pirates waltz in here
and take their crew member back,
what does that say about our forces?
We have to beat them!
Our pride is on the line!
Those Straw Hats are going to learn not to take us lightly.
Hey, gatekeeper!
What's going on at the main gate?
Can you hear me or what?
How many enemies are we looking at here?
Where are they right now?
I need answers, main gate!
Did something happen?
What's wrong?
Hello?
I can't help you if you don't help me first!
You didn't call me an attacker, did you?
Are you listening?
Go, Baxon!
The guy!
No!
Bazzucco Bat!
We're just starting!
I can't go wasting my ammo!
Go in through the doors on the side!
Open that gate!
Push them back before it's too late!
You're in the way!
Modu, take the left!
You've got it!
You're not going anywhere!
Is that a nose hair?
Actually, it's a cowlick!
Get moving!
Fanked, I owe you one!
My team, my car!
Yeah!
Are you done?
Mozu!
Gateway!
We tear ships apart.
You can't expect a little block to slow us down.
All right, my side is done!
Mine too!
Good!
Let's open those gates!
Herculean destroyers, go!
Don't let them open the gates!
Fire!
All right, men, let's go!
Let's go!
Whoa!
What is that big hole?
We don't have time for that right now!
Just ignore it!
Everyone make a dash to the next gate!
It's a waterfall!
We did it!
Guys, over here!
I got a plan!
Could you lend me a hand?
Yeah!
Kashi!
Mimo!
You have to get up!
We need your help!
The main gate was forced to open by intruders!
Hey, Oimo!
You hear that?
You said the main gate's open!
Ohoy!
I'm afraid that won't do!
Right, Kashi?
And I was sleeping so well, too!
Work is work!
Let's go!
We'll see you next time.
We won't even let an ant through this gate.
Good thing we aren't ants.
This is your last chance to turn around and go home.
One more step and we'll stop you.
The only thing that matters is getting through that gate.
We came here to rescue our big bro and that's just what we're gonna do.
On the next, One Piece, battle against giants.
Open the second gate.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!